No, come quiet!
I am in my shell!
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
Behold, they're king and the compass!
Yikes!
That is what a taste of our fury.
Do you yield?
I do not.
Thank you.
I finally found it.
And now that one can start.
We're the Mario Brothers
and Plumbing's again.
We're not like the others
who get all the fame.
When you think he's in, Ramo,
you could call us on the double.
We're faster than the others
you'll be hooked on the brothers.
It's me.
Am I?
I'm the Luigi.
Are you a player to be
paying too much for plumbing?
I'm a man.
That's why this is a Mario Brothers are me.
To save Brooklyn.
That's the queen.
And the old Alex.
Thank you, Super Mario Bros.
It seems like the only thing you
haven't dreamed is my bank account.
So, kid, do the expensive, a
plumbing company, so when you're
adjustin' face, with the soap for
the Mario Brothers, you're family.
On the brothers, the brothers,
the brothers, the brothers.
Wow, you were great.
I was great.
Are you kidding me?
You were great.
I am so glad we spent our
life savings on this commercial.
That is not a commercial.
That is cinema.
What about the accents?
Is it, is it too much?
Too much.
It's a perfect.
Wahoo!
Okay, I'm gonna trust you.
Well, well, well.
If it is in Brooklyn's favorite
failures, the stupid Mario Brothers.
Oh, great.
Spikes here.
Hey, Spike.
Yeah.
It's on me!
Thank you.
Ooh, yeah.
Tell me.
Have you even gotten
one call since you left me to
start your dumb company
as a matter of fact, Spike?
We have.
Wow, really?
Uh, yeah.
I'm mom called, and she said, oh boy, is
that the best commercial I've ever seen?
And I said, thank you very much, Mother.
We're very proud of it.
So bold.
Good luck running the
business with this idiot.
Say that again about my
brother and you're gonna regret it.
Oh, yeah?
Get this to your tiny brain, Mario.
You're a joke and you always will be.
Are you insane?
He's three times in size.
Luigi, come on.
You know, you can't be scared all the time.
You'd be surprised.
Hello, Super Mario brothers.
Uh-huh.
A drip in your faucet.
That's great.
I mean, that's great.
You call us because we can be
there and we can fix it right away.
Okay.
Mario, we got one!
Ha-ha!
The Super Mario Brothers are his business!
Woo-hoo!
I know.
We're gonna be late.
No, we're not.
Come on.
Let's go.
There you go!
No!
All right!
What are you doing?
Yeah!
All right!
Get off of it!
You can't see it.
Come on, let's go!
Oh wow, we have hit the big die
The drip is right upstairs
at the end of the hall.
Can you fix it?
Very confident, sir.
You'll be careful about making a mess.
Ma'am, I assure you, we don't make messes.
We fix them.
That's Francis.
He likes you.
Mama, mama, mama, mama, mama, yeah, baby.
French.
And a first job complete.
Hey!
Francis is here.
Uh, Mario?
That hell out is gonna escape!
No, he won't.
Mario?
Who's good on me yet?
Who's a good boy?
Found the problem
Oh, it's the Super Mario
Brothers from the TV.
They gave an Oscar for worst actors.
What I do.
So, uh, is everybody
saw the commercial then?
Eh, we've seen it.
And I wouldn't quit your day job.
Oops, he already did.
Well, I thought it was incredible.
It belonged in a movie theater.
Oh, mushrooms.
Everybody loves mushrooms, right?
I like mushrooms.
I'll take it.
Mario, seriously?
Well, what were you
thinking with that commercial?
What?
It's supposed to be funny.
It's a little bit of a bad, yeah,
but what's with the outfits?
Farmers were in white clouds.
That's right.
You got to have a trademark.
Got to stand out.
Don't listen to them.
The world laughed at Da Vinci, too.
I'm not sure they did, ma.
Dad, what did you think?
I think you're nuts.
You don't leave a steady
job for some crazy dream.
And the worst part, you're
bringing your brother down with you.
Well, thanks, Dad.
Thanks for your support.
What'd I say?
Hey.
You're not bringing me down?
You know what?
What do they know, huh?
That's not just them.
I hope life's everyone's
telling us we can't do this.
We can't do that.
Just sick and tired of feeling so small.
Everything is under control, I promise you.
We are very close to fixing this.
That's somebody else,
somebody safe, rocklers!
Save Brooklyn?
Which?
This is our chance.
Destiny is calling.
Destiny del Vacho from high school.
What?
No!
Just come on.
Hey, hey, hey, been
looking in the right place.
Come on, Lou.
You are not seriously concerned.
Fire of y'all.
You got to get to that pressure valve.
I knew saving Brooklyn was a bad idea.
Come on.
Whoa.
What is this place?
Looks like nobody's
been down here for years.
Luigi?
Luigi are you in there?
What?
I'm telling you, I think it hurt
us as long as we're together.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
That one's perfectly fine.
That's a little mushroom.
Man, how do mushroom man talking to me?
Who's the major?
I'm tow.
Uh, Mario.
So this is, uh, this is not a dream?
That hurt, right?
Yes!
Definitely not a dream.
And then, this place is...
The Mushroom Kingdom!
My shrooms, apparently.
And that is a cruel twist of faith.
Yeah, I'm actually looking for somebody.
My brother, in fact.
He looks exactly like me,
but tall and skinny and green.
See, last time I saw him,
he was falling into a pipe.
It was foggy and I believe there was lava.
That is not good.
Your brother has landed in the dark lands.
They're under bowsers control.
I was there.
He's the most evil,
wretched creature alive.
I'm taking you to see the princess.
She can help you.
She can do anything.
Princess?
Come on, Mario.
Our big adventure begins now.
Hang on, Luigi.
Mario?
Where are you?
Ha ha!
Yes!
You just got... Hello, Eejid!
This way, Mario, the
princess looks right on that hill.
Got a big adventure happening right now.
Let's do a path for us.
If I could just... Here you go.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, everybody!
Come and go!
This guy's brother is going to die!
Immidentally!
Out of the way, please!
He's trying to clear a path.
That's all I'm doing.
He's gonna be fine.
Shit, Trill!
I see a button!
Does this thing work?
Yes, we're gonna break it.
You just have to blow it to it.
And... We go?
Right off.
Whoa!
Okay, so these bricks
are just floating here.
Just popping this bite
that we're on our way.
The only way to fly, man,
Oh, wow.
Love these pipes.
Oh!
Here we are!
Palastores!
Big, big, boom!
Come on!
Whoa!
Pretty impressive, am I right?
Oh, it right there, you two.
Oh, hey, I need to see the princess.
It's an emergency.
What princess?
I never heard of any princess.
Wait, I did.
A princess, though, isn't another castle.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You should try another castle, maybe.
She ain't in this one.
Huh?
OK, so they're messing with you.
And I don't like it.
What do you guys, um,
what do you want to eat?
Anything, anything your heart's designed.
Go.
I am ready to scramble it up.
Hey, intrude.
Council, your attention.
Bowser has found the superstar
and is headed toward our kingdom.
Its power will make him invincible.
We will be destroyed.
Princess, what are we gonna do?
I will not let him hurt you.
We are going to stop Bowser.
How?
Look at us.
We're adorable.
I'm going to convince the
great Kong army to help us.
Together, we'll annihilate that monster.
Their mad king doesn't make alliances.
The Kongs will never agree.
I can convince him.
I'll leave for the jungle
kingdom in the morning.
Good luck, Princess, for all our sakes.
Princess!
Wait!
Release him!
Are you?
These are human!
I mean, you are a human, right?
It's just, you're so small.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, let's go back.
Where did you come from?
Me and my little brother
Luigi, we fell down this
pipe, and now he's lost,
somewhere in the dark lands.
Then it's only a matter of time
until he's captured by Bowser.
But you're in luck.
I'm on my way to stop him.
Well, take me with you.
This guy's a lunatic, a psycho.
He will eat you for breakfast.
He won't even notice it probably
because you're very, very small.
You know what?
Make fun of me all you want.
But you're gonna help me find my brother.
Please?
Okay.
Let's see what you're made of.
Is that a yes?
No.
That's a let's see what you're made of.
I'm sorry.
If you can finish this,
you're coming with me.
Watch and learn.
That was amazing.
Wait.
How am I supposed to do that?
With the power-ups.
They give us special abilities.
Really?
Go on.
Eat it.
Now, this has to be a mushroom,
because I just hate mushrooms in.
Okay?
Mm.
Are you sure there's not like a... Yeah!
Yep, there it is, and all gone.
Hop.
Mm.
Oh, not cool!
Mm?
Oh!
Mm!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I'm tall.
And strong.
And you can jump.
I got this.
No problem.
Oh, yeah.
When you get hit, you lose the power.
Great!
Come on!
Bye again!
Well, we have a long journey
ahead of us, Moustache.
But I didn't make it.
You almost did?
No one gets it right away.
How many tries did it take you?
Oh, so many.
I was not good at it.
Worse than you.
You got it right away, didn't you?
I got it right away, but I grew up here.
Okay, now you're just
trying to make me feel better.
No.
Is it working?
A little bit.
Yeah.
My army!
Super!
Go first!
Whatever those things are, after
years of searching for the superstar,
it is finally our time now, the
most powerful title in the world!
Soon we will arrive at the Mushroom
Kingdom, where every years of being
sworn enemies, I will ask their princess
to marry me in a fairy tale wedding!
Did he say, Mary, their princess?
Doesn't she hate you?
Of course, she hates me.
But that makes me love her all the more.
Her heart-shaped bangs.
The way she floats in the breeze.
Her immovable tiara.
And when she sees this star,
oh-ho-ho-ho wedding bells.
Oh, what if she says no?
Then I will power up with this star
and destroy them at their kingdom.
Prepare yourselves for
the best wedding ever.
It's gonna run!
They're all counting on us.
No pressure.
My codes.
Our days of terror are almost over.
With the help of the
Kong army, we will stop.
Ugh, who's he?
He's not important.
Nervous?
Who?
Me?
Yes.
A little.
We're going on an adventure.
Come on, guys!
Did it, did it, did it, did it.
Hey, Mario.
You know this guy?
We're best friends.
But are we?
Don't worry.
I will protect you.
A toad brave enough to join me.
I fear nothing.
Well, that tells it.
You're coming with us.
Let's move.
After we're going on, I tend to.
Whoo!
Pretty incredible, huh?
Mom, me.
I'll never let anyone ruin this.
You're so cool.
And with my style we're gonna rule.
Peach, understand.
I'm on the love you tell the very end.
We just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just
be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be,
just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just
be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just be, just
The prince has been training him.
They are up to something, Sia.
Sit.
Jam with me.
This, er, human, where did he come from?
He...
I'm sure?
Does the princess like him?
Sire, look in the mirror!
You'll have nothing to worry about.
I know that.
Now who he is and what they're planning?
I'm on it, son.
May I lift the cover?
Not yet.
Pain is the best teacher.
No.
Thinking about your brother?
We've never been a part this long.
Don't worry.
We're going to save him.
You don't seem like you're from here.
I don't know where I'm from.
Really?
Yep.
My earliest memory is arriving.
I was so lucky they found me.
I took me in.
Raised me like one of their own.
And when I was ready,
They made me their princess.
It may be you from my world.
There's a huge universe
out there with a lot of galaxies.
you
Thank you.
What is your name?
Luigi.
Not sure if you know who I am, but I'm about
to marry a princess and rule the world.
Wow.
Yay.
But there's one problem, Luigi.
There's a human traveling with my fiance.
Has a mustache just like you.
Do you know him?
No.
Tough one, I see.
Maybe this will get you to talk.
You think I know every human
being with a mustache wearing an
identical outfit with a hat with
a letter of his first name on it?
Because I don't.
Do you know him?
I know him.
He's my brother Mario and
he's the best guy in the world.
Do princesses find him attractive?
They do as they have good days.
Get him out of my sight.
We'll see how tough this Mario is
when he watches me kill his brother.
Where am I?
Home.
Hey, him, no heed.
He is cute, but he is.
In the same world, it is the
same who is called crazy.
How long you guys been in here?
Time, like hoping, isn't illusion.
Please, we are depressed enough.
There's gotta be a way out of here.
There's no escape, but only hope.
Is this really a death?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
You ready?
Sure.
What?
How are you doing?
We are here to see the king.
Follow me.
That gorilla's wearing a sports coat.
I feel underdressed.
Oh, by all means, come in.
Great and mighty cranky con.
So, I heard you want my army.
Yes, your Highness, without your help,
the Mushroom Kingdom will be annihilated.
What makes you think
you're worthy of fighting
alongside the greatest
army in the world?
Because we have heart, and
with your strength, we can win.
Okay, fight.
That's it?
No, that's not it.
The answer is no.
Goodbye.
If the Mushroom Kingdom
falls, the Jungle Kingdom is next.
We're not leaving without your army.
This guy.
Oh, he makes me laugh.
Alright, tough guy.
You want my army so badly?
Defeat my son in the great rig of Kong!
Give us a second?
This is a really, really bad idea.
What do you have another
way to save my brother?
Are you two done whispering?
It's a little rude.
You, sir, have a deal.
I'll fight you, son, and win.
I'm sure you will.
I said simmer down.
That means you did he called me.
Sorry.
Now, since I want this
fight to last more than
five seconds, I put power
ups around the arena.
You're welcome, Mario.
I don't need anything special to
break every bone in your tiny body.
All right.
Okay, guess you're not getting my army.
It's this way you came for.
It is on like Donkey Kong.
You're about to pick on
someone your own size.
Yeah!
I guess he got the wrong mushroom.
That enough?
Not even close.
He looks adorable.
He really does.
Oh, what am I?
You got the cat box!
Oh my... Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Now you die.
I'm a cat.
Meow.
I had enough.
Not even close.
I'll take that as a yes.
That was incredible.
You kept feeding you senseless
and you just kept getting back up.
You just don't know when to quit.
Huh.
Well, never thought
of that as a good thing.
It's a great thing.
Thanks.
Nice.
I let him win, just for the record.
Really, though?
Why would you do that?
You want to know why?
It's my new old business, that's what!
All right, giant monkey.
Enough!
Get inside!
We've located Bowser's ship.
He's gonna arrive at the
mushroom kingdom by sundown.
Lucky for you guys, I got a short climb.
We beat him there and ambush him.
Yeah, I know.
That's why we're gonna need carts.
What are you waiting for?
Pick your cards!
I hate you.
To the mushroom kingdom
and the biggest fight of our lives.
Here?
Princess Beach?
Here we are.
I guess love really makes
a guy come out of his shell.
Let's rule the world together forever.
Will you marry me?
We have found the princess
and the moustacheal human.
He has defeated Donkey
Kong and won the Kong army.
So, like, pitch was super impressed?
It appears so, yes.
They are heading to their secret passage.
Or they think they can surprise me, huh?
Two can play at that game.
No one panic, but the road is about to end.
What?
Is there anything like this in your world?
No.
We don't drive on rainbows.
What are you going to tell me next?
The turtles are evil?
No, no.
And usually pets.
No.
What?
Act on the broken up by your turtle.
Maybe I will.
Is this you flirting?
This is painful, because
I was trying to be nice.
You are so embarrassing.
A princess would never go out with you.
Yes, she would.
I guarantee she would.
High you.
Enough.
All right, all right.
Watch out.
No, that's a position!
Mario, you're a shitman!
Split up!
Yeah!
You did not!
That is how you princess!
Uh-oh!
You can't escape me!
What?
Blue shell!
No!
No, Mario!
Get your cow claws off of me!
Goodbye, Mario.
We have to get home!
Hey!
This is your fault!
My fault!
You're the one who died!
I don't want the last
thing I hear before I die!
To be gone!
Are you?
You saved my life.
Yeah, well, I won't tell anyone.
Good, please don't.
Okay.
Did you just feel something?
We lost the army.
And Mario's gone.
Bowser is coming.
Head into the forest.
I'll buy you some time.
You heard her, evacuate the city.
Go with the others.
I said I wouldn't let anyone hurt you.
Princess Peach.
Brave as ever.
As you can see, I have the superstar.
If you're going to use it, use it now.
No, Princess, I stole this star for us.
I guess love really makes
a guy come out of his shell.
I told you that line wouldn't work.
Pictures, with this star,
we will be invincible.
We can rule the world together forever.
Will you marry me?
Mary, are you insane?
I would never marry you.
Maybe you should reconsider.
Please stop!
Oh, Mary, you just don't hurt my toes.
You have my word.
I'm ready.
Life is sad, isn't this sad?
Life and prison is very, very sad.
Ooh, fresh meat for the grinder.
Who's this ray of sunshine?
There's no sunshine.
Only darkness.
Shout out to the children!
Oh, prisoners.
You don't deserve this, but
you're invited to the Royal Wedding!
Yay!
Well, you will love your
ritualistically sacrifice!
Oh, no, no!
Finally, mercy!
Mario!
So this is the end.
Being slowly digested by an
eel next to an idiot in overalls.
But at least your brother
isn't gonna die because of you.
You should not gonna die with
your dad thinking you're a joke.
I don't mind my dad thinks I'm a joke too.
Yeah.
Well.
Your dad's right.
Know what?
Feel bad enough.
Just leave me alone.
I've never met your dad,
but he sounds brilliant.
Just go in a corner and smash
some stuff, smash monkey.
I...
I'll smash this thing!
This was amazing!
Now we're leaving!
Princess, I got it.
Great job.
Couldn't have you going out
there without your bouquet?
It's perfect.
I'll be sacrificing them in your honor.
Lower the prisoners!
You really thought I'd marry you?
Kinda?
I'd never marry a monster.
Then we are breaking up right now!
They gotta be up there!
You wanna do this?
Yes, I do.
Hey, what is this do?
Cool raccoon suit.
Really?
No.
Whoa!
Mario!
I told you, see?
He's going to be together.
He's going to be okay.
Mario, why do you look like a bear?
What is this?
You're a good kid.
Make your pecs dance.
You deserve it.
No time now.
Definitely later.
Launch the Banner Bill and
destroy the mushroom king of!
Hey, hey, hey over here!
Oh, yeah.
Come on.
A little closer.
One more.
That's beautiful.
You made this right.
Huh?
Rockwood?
You want this?
You ruined my wedding!
I would finally gonna be happy!
Now you will suffer!
Like greed!
You really thought you could stop me?
You worthless wee little nothing.
Come out and fight!
Or are you too scared?
I'm a man!
That's why the Super
Mario brothers are here!
I'll do save a Brooklyn!
Save a Brooklyn!
That's a girl!
Leave him alone.
Mario, you just don't know when to quit.
Yeah, I've been told that before.
Mario!
No!
That's mine!
Ah!
Move!
I think it hurt us.
As long as we're together.
Move!
Ripping the pieces!
Peaches.
Listen, this is not the way I pictured
it, but give me one more chance.
Ew, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
And Luigi, you're so brave.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, it's kind of my thing.
Ah, my boy, my hero.
Whoa!
Mario, you know, are amazing.
Thanks, Dad.
I'll bring it in.
Let's hear it for the Super Mario Brothers!
These are my boys!
Hey!
Wahoo!
Yes!
Thank you.
Now that's a happy ending.
Or is it?
Because everything's over now.
And all that's left is
you and the infinite void.
Kind of makes you want
to play saxophone, huh?
Yeah.
A thousand troops a
couple could who keep me
for new Princess Peach
at the end of the line.
I'll make you mine.
Hey!
Wait in there!
Let's out, little guy!
You time training like this!
Do you know who I am?
Yeah.
You
you
Oh, yeah.